As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try!
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're said to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun!
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled!
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace.
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found!
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous!
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Do you have to thank for that?
huh?
a zombie's only purpose
is to serve its master.
i made you and i can.
unmake you just as easily.
it's strange.
it seems as if the original owner
of the body is fighting back.
yeah but that person
died over 10 years ago.
does that mean a body without
a soul can still have.
a will of its own.
who can really say.
even if we read every book in
every library in the world.
we
wouldn't know.
I will kill both of them. There we go!
That's the Century I know in lab!
Good to have you back!
Try to buy me some time, okay?
I'm getting the hell out of
here! It's a shame.
For a moment, I actually
thought a miracle had happened.
It's time It's time for dos et Balls!
You get back here!
Uh-oh, it sounds like
oars has finally returned!
You stupid pirate deer!
Why are you siding with a
corpse instead of a genius?
Let me go!
You're not even human to begin with, so
what the hell do you even care, you monster?
The captain of our crew is just
fine with monsters like me.
And mossheads and
perverts and cyborgs, too.
And all of us get along just fine.
And unlike you,
our captain doesn't
need to turn people into
zombie slaves to get them to listen to it.
I don't care.
Let me go. No!
Certainly.
Leave it to me.
Pierre Nafleur.
Why do I suddenly feel
as if I'm walking on air?
Oh!
Help me!
I'm out, Dr. Chopper.
Let's be reasonable.
Try to consider the
consequences here for a moment.
If you splatter my genius brains
all over the floor right now,
you'd be doing a disservice
to the medical community.
I don't care.
That genius brain of yours is
even more rotten than your zombie.
I thought you were a man of reason, Dr.
Chopper.
Can't we work something out?
Eat this.
Now, Robin Chopper Suplex!
This guy's even bigger than a
giant is that really my zombie?
You've kept me waiting haven't you?
Whores it seems your body and
shadow have finally fused properly.
I take it you'll be obedient from now on
let's find out answer
me who is your master?
Gecko Moria you are my master!
No way!
Hey, what the hell do
you think you're saying?
I thought you were
supposed to be my shadow?
You don't have to listen
to this guy, he sucks!
Huh?
Who are you?
And what's with that dumb hat?
Now that everything is in order,
let me give you your first mission.
These dastardly fellows are causing a
ruckus on your poor master's island!
They're called the Straw Hat pirates.
Find them.
Crush every last one of them and
then put them back on their ship.
If you kill one or two
of them it's no problem.
Besides the bounties are
over a hundred million so
they won't fall apart after
a few punches even from you.
So don't hold back!
I want to see every ounce of your power!
Understand?
Okay you got it, master.
Oh, found one.
It's Straw Hat.
So long, Straw Hat. What?
You're running away?
Get back here!
Come, come!
Hey, that's my move!
You jerk! Ah!
That...
that's Luffy's zombie! Oh, help!
The floor's going to collapse!
Chopper, over here, quickly!
Got it!
Wow, that was a close one.
That giant...
is Luffy?
Hogbeck and Shandora
fell to the floor below,
and it doesn't look like they're moving.
Too heavy.
Damn it!
Oh, Century, hurry up.
Get over here and move this rock.
This isn't funny, Century.
I really need your help right now.
Ours is going to crush me
like a giant cockroach.
I can't die.
I'm far too smart to die.
I have so much left to give.
I'm your master, damn it.
Why are you just standing there? Hurry!
I can't move.
My body won't move. Say what?
Enough already.
I don't want to hear anymore.
The only will a zombie has
is the will to follow orders.
So hurry up and save me.
You're nothing but a
corpse with a pretty face.
Don't pretend you're human.
Hey, I'm dyin' here, Century!
Boris is gonna stop me!
AAAAAAAAHHHHH!
Oh, it's like down here!
Watch where you're stepping down at!
It's me, you oaf!
You'd still be dead in a block of ice
right now if it wasn't for my genius!
AAAAAAAH!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
That last tremor was one thing, but this
feels like the whole mansion's coming down!
It's the Loopy Zombie!
Uh-oh.
That doesn't sound good.
What's going on here?
Crap, what now?
Is that thing Luffy's zombie?
Damn it.
Nami, hey, now would be
a good time to wake up.
There's nothing I can do.
Guess I'm just gonna have to run for it.
Hey, Nami?
Nami?
She just disappeared.
It's you again.
Looks like the tables have turned.
You bastard.
So you're still alive, huh?
If you want to finish this,
stop hiding and bring it on.
Well, well.
That troublemaking giant is
finally under our control.
In other words, you're screwed.
I think I'll be taking my
bride for good this time.
Like hell you will.
You give Nami back.
Where the hell are you hiding her?
Ah, are you lonely?
Then why don't you play with Oz here?
Oh, man!
It's some kind of giant monster!
Mercy!
That's...
it's a zombie!
Oh, crap!
That must be Luffy's zombie!
Hey, look down there!
Someone else came out of the building
and it looks like Chef Curly Brows!
Damn it!
I failed her.
What the hell is he doing?
He's gonna get stomped on!
Are you running from your
shadow or chasing me?
Giant monster me is gonna be a problem But
if I wanna get everyone's shadows back,
I guess I'm gonna have to
beat you anyway, aren't I?
So get back here! Ahhh!
Too bad, but it looks like
the last laugh belongs to me.
She's still out cold.
I'll take her someplace safe.
Don't you worry.
It may be in private, but
we'll have our wedding yet.
My sleeping beauty.
Is Mistress Perona all right?
I think so.
She passed out, but it doesn't
look like she was injured.
Where's Captain Cougar?
Did the long-nosed guy purify him?
How did this happen?
Let's get out of here.
This mansion's as good as done for.
We can let the special zombie take
care of the Straw Hats for us.
This is rough, man.
We gotta get out of here, like, right now.
The special zombie's going on a rampage!
I'm showing back to my grave! Look!
He's taller than the mansion!
He's just stomping over everything!
We could be next!
That is not good!
Usopp!
Hey, Robin! Chopper!
We're in trouble here!
Big trouble!
The Luffy zombie has our faces!
No, wait, I mean on his arm.
He has our wanted posters.
Oh, man.
This is no joke.
He's got to understand.
Show yourselves.
Come out, Straw Hats.
But you can't hide from me!
Damn it, Luffy.
Your zombie's gonna be
a real pain in the ass.
Come on, Captain, you're not gonna
tear apart your own crew, are you?
It seems he's been given the order.
I just hope the real Luffy is all right.
Don't eat me, I'm all bones!
Are we supposed to fight that damn thing?
No way!
Wait!
Merde!
Come and get me, Straw Hat! Huh?
Well, I'll be.
Who put this dead end here?
Did it occur to you that I'm
keeping you busy chasing after me?
Oh, while your entire crew gets
slaughtered by your own shadow?
Jackass!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
What is that thing?
It's terrifying!
Wait, is that...
Hey! Usopp!
Is this you down there?
Zoro!
What are you doing up there?
There's Franky too!
And look, Brooke is with them!
They're all safe!
For now.
Hey, you're standing in my damn way.
And what are you doing interfering?
What's gotten into you, Luffy?
He's my enemy.
My name's Orz.
Hello there.
Look at this that moron's picking a fight
with the monster that damn stupid cook?
Has he even rescued Nami yet?
Probably not.
I think he's in worse
trouble than she is now.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Sandy's in trouble.
This is unexpected.
I was under the impression That all
they wanted from us were our shadows.
But he looks more primed for violence.
I guess They decided they already got the
cream of the crop with Luffy's shadow.
Scary.
It's scary.
No way we can Fight that thing.
You
look
just the same
as your wanted poster.
But you admit you're part of
the pirate. The crew, huh?
Yeah, one of it!
Go! Go!
Luffy's move!
Oh, crap, can he stretch?
Did he get Luffy's rubber
powers with his shadow?
Circle!
Okay, he didn't stretch,
but does it really matter?
With that strength and with as long as his
reach is, it's basically the same thing!
Ours.
I knew I recognized that name.
It's him, the demon from the legends,
It's once known as the Continent Polar.
Ko-ya-yay-free!
Stop it!
How can something that big move that fast?
Oh, crap!
He's got him now!
No! Stop it!
Sachi, look out!
All right, Pyreng!
Splishing time!
Firebird star!
I'm...
I'm sorry!
Oh
Tall woman with black hair,
that's the little fuzzy thing
This is bad Franky we gotta
do something drawn this way
I think this will get his attention!
Hang on! I gotcha!
You guys get down to the lower roof fast!
One gorilla, two gorilla!
Three-sword style, double gorilla!
What?!
Now Kaku...
Volcano!
Throw! Holy crap! What do we do?
Even if that punch didn't kill him,
there's no way he can survive
falling from that height!
Take this, you monster!
Weapons left!
He dodged it again?
How could he be that angel?
What's he doing now?
Ahhhh!
Franky, no!
Skeleton guy!
Saro's falling towards us! Oh, crap!
He'll die if he hits the ground!
Donut blue, add spider in there!
I owe you one, Robert.
Damn it.
Whoa!
You might be huge, but
you're still a zombie!
Special attack, Soul Star!
It wasn't...
It wasn't enough!
He's too big!
Now have he gone!
Luffy, you jerk.
I don't know you.
My name's not Luffy.
Member, Moria's servant.
Name's Ours?